welcome back
today we are going to see what it takes to get a good source of dragon blood
more specifically
how to get the draconic fusion crafter
that thing requires end game materials from all of the magic mods
so let's get started from the first item
the bloody ichorium fusion casing
and all magic mods are rebalanced around thaumcraft
so here we are
after getting a witches oven
we start extracting random breaths from saplings
then we farm some questionable plants
to get the ingredients to make a nice soup
okay just kidding
that's not edible
we just made some compost
a really weird compost
since instead of growing plants
it mutates them
and those mutated plants will give off a whiff of magic when burned
which is required for an attuned stone
required to craft Greg's altar
thus finally allowing us to start blood magic
this is a really funny mod
that is all about taking blood tests
you just have to keep puncturing yourself
until you almost faint out
and then we soak items inside that pool of tomato sauce
however all of those blood losses are not healthy
so we made a personal healing nano booster to keep in check
and we charge it wirelessly
with that
we can now have some peak game play
just look at how much life essence of mouse with a weight stuck on it is making
we just have to change the items in the chest every now and then
until we rush the whole tier 5 altar
but then we find out
we also have to do other things for our dragon blood blocks
but since we are blind
and can't see there's a missing chalk
we shall go back to witchery in frustration
here we rush an altar to power the distillery
we rushed without taking recordings
but to do some quests
we make a kettle
and start brewing some potions of love
which is somehow part of a sleeping potion
guess you gotta love sleeping
and after taking a nice sip
we lose all of our stuff
and I don't understand how that's a nightmare any more than doing those magic mods
anyways
that didn't seem to be required for getting what we needed some chalks
so we just skip quests and get those
which we use to make a ritual helper
which isn't really helping much
anyways after figuring it out
we managed to make the magic circle appear
and produce a blood powered sword
with that we collect some weak shards
that will be required later on
then to stop having to do peak gameplay
we build the well of suffering
that thing will make blood using mobs
and it can even work with a mob farm
finally we no longer have to stuck ourselves onto that annoying thing
and we move it below our main altar
now
while our blood passively builds up
we can go summon a demon
so that we can kill him to get some shards
next
we start melting random stuff
to make some colorful lamps
which we place on our newly built altar
once every lamp shoots the center
we can start the new ritual
the convocation of the damned
and when the pyrotechnics are done
we can sacrifice a demon on top of it
thus creating a portal that will start building an ever expanding town
this place will spawn the demons
that will drop the shards we needed
and since we will need a lot
we set up an industrial mob farm for those
the first usage will be making an ichorium block
which we soak into blood right away
and that was the first part of our draconic crafter
the second one is more neat
and requires the funny flower mod by Vazkii
so we start making a stone pot
for watering the funny flowers
we use that to merge some random flowers into other flowers
and the first mutated flower should be a pure daisy
which can enchant blocks around it
with those new blocks
we can craft a mana pool where we can't even swim
and a mana spreader
that will concentrate mana into beams
with those two and a couple more of flowers
we start filling up our pool with mana
and I have no idea if this is even working
or how much mana we are making
but the real question here is why we are doing that
never mind
let's follow the guide
to get the gaia plate for our draconic crafter
after throwing stuff into our mana pool
it turns more bluish in color
and that blue stuff was needed for our combustion generator plant
that plants turns burnable fuels into mana
at the price of lag and items despawned
however that Mana was still not enough
luckily Asgardandelion came in and help
with a nice plant that does not cause lag
nor other annoying things
next instead of filling a pool
we use our mana on an altar to craft runes
and here we have some more peak gameplay
watching random items jumping around a stone while taking shots from some random wood contraptions feeding from random flowers
and since we are going to do this just a dozen of times
all with different recipes
I see no point in even looking into if there is a way of automating that thing
once it starts sparkling
we can throw in a rock and complete the process
we repeat that funny peek gameplay process for 50 times
4 for each rune we can make
and then we hope we will never ever have to do that ever again
once we have all the runes set on the thumcraft altar
we infuse those into a terrestrial agglomeration plane
which once again
will ask us to drop four items on it
and hope they don't despawn before the process of unknown duration is completed
to avoid risks
we instead use a pool as a buffer
and some sparks to make random lights turn on
so that we can lag in FPS other than TPS
and that yielded us some Terra steel
and we had to spam a lot of things to make more at a decent speed
and the thing we use that Terra Steel for is an elven portal
which is a portal that we throw trash in to get some trash out
with that new trash
we can craft the gaia pylon required to summon on annoying boss
unlike the rest of the mod
this boss doesn't have any color or cool looking particle
and it is also immune to projectiles for some reason
after defeating it
we are rewarded with some gaia spirit
which we use to make our frist gaia spirit ingot
and summon a friend of the previous boss
and now we just farm more of those annoying things
until we have enough for the dense gaia plate required for our draconic fusion crafter
once we build the new machine
we quickly make one ender dragon egg
then
we can make the dragon blood out of mundane materials
but once we tried to do so
we run into an issue
we need to bring this machine up to tier 3
that requires wyvern fusion casings
which we can almost do
the main issue there is that
we need a mining module mk3 for our space elevator
and while crafting that was an easy task
to use it
we also need MK3 space elevator motors
and those are going to require a couple of weird materials
which we shall make in an appropriate sci-fi high tech episode
so what's the lesson there
yeah after all
maybe bees are not that annoying to make use or manage
and they are also evolving
and starting to make electronics
so see you next season for motor bee
bye bye
欢迎回来！
今天我们来找找龙血的优秀来源
更具体地说
是要获得龙研聚合装置
那东西需要所有魔法mod的最终材料
所以让我们从第一项开始
血腥灵宝聚合机械方块
所有魔法mod都围绕神秘时代魔改了
来吧
在得到女巫烤箱后
我们开始从树苗中提取随机熏气
然后种植一些奇异植物
来获得一碗美味汤料的配料
好吧，开玩笑的
那可不能吃
我们刚做了些堆肥
一种非常奇怪的堆肥
因为它不催熟作物
而是让其变异
那些变异的植物在燃烧时会产生魔力之息
这是调谐之石所必需的
用来制造血魔法祭坛
这样我们就可以开始血魔法了
这是一个非常有趣/奇怪/幽默的mod
全是关于抽血化验的
你只需要持续刺伤自己
直到几乎晕倒
然后我们把东西浸泡在番茄酱池里
然而，失血对健康不好
所以我们做了个个人治疗纳米加速器来保持健康
并给它无线充电
有了那个
我们可以来点高端操作
看看通过压着鼠标产生了多少生命精华
我们只需要时不时地更换箱子里的物品
直到我们速通五级祭坛
但后来我们发现
我们还要为龙血块做其他事情
但因为我们视力不好
没看到少了一个粉笔痕迹
我们沮丧地回到巫术中
在这里，我们冲一个祭坛来为酿酒厂供电
这里没有记录下来
但是要做一些任务
我们做一个水壶
开始酿造一些爱之酿药水
这是安眠药的一部分
我猜你一定喜欢睡觉
喝了一口后
我们失去了所有的东西
这是个噩梦
但比不上玩这些魔法mod噩梦
不管怎样
结果那些好像根本没必要
我们要的不过就是几支粉笔
所以我们跳过任务去拿那些
我们用它来做仪式帮手
这并没有多大帮助
反正弄清楚后
我们设法让魔法阵出现了
制造一把由血驱动的剑
我们用它收集一些虚弱气血碎片
以后会用得到
为了结束顶级游戏体验
我们建造苦难之井
那东西会利用生物制造血
它甚至可以与工业屠宰场合作
我们终于不用再做烦人的抽血了
我们把它移到主祭坛下面
现在
当我们的血液被动地积聚
我们可以去召唤恶魔
杀掉他获得一些碎片
接下来
我们开始融化乱七八糟的物品
做一些五颜六色的灯
放在我们新建的祭坛上
一旦每盏灯都射向中心
我们可以开始新的仪式
恶魔入侵
烟火表演结束后
我们可以在上面献祭一个恶魔
产生一个会不断扩建城镇的传送门
这地方会滋生恶魔
恶魔掉落我们需要的碎片
既然我们需要很多
我们为他们建立工业屠宰场
第一个用途是灵宝块
马上把它浸泡在血液里
这是我们龙研的第一部分
第二个更整洁
需要Vazkii制作的奇怪花朵mod
所以我们开始做一个石锅
给奇怪的花浇水
我们用它来把一些杂七杂八的花合并成其他的花
第一朵变异的花是白雏菊
它可以把周围的方块转换
用这些新方块
我们可以做一个浅得不能游泳的魔力池
和魔力发射器
来将魔力聚焦成束流
有了这两个方块和一些花朵
可以开始填满魔力池了
我不知道这是否在工作
或者已经有了多少魔力
但真正的问题是我们为什么要这么做
没关系
让我们跟随任务书
来获得龙研要的盖亚板
把东西扔进法力池后
它的颜色变得更蓝
这是燃烧发电植物所需要的
这植物将燃料转化为法力
而代价是卡顿和物品消失
不过法力还是不够
幸运的是有阿斯加德蒲公英
这是一种不会卡顿的花
也没有其他烦人的事情
接下来不是填满魔力池
我们用魔力在祭坛上制造符文
在这我们有更顶级的游戏体验
看一堆乱七八糟的道具在石头旁边乱蹦
还要被那些靠着随便几朵花供能的木头玩意射击
既然我们要做十几次符文
每个都有不同的配方
搞自动化完全没必要
一旦它开始闪闪发光
我们可以扔一块石头完成整个过程
我们重复这个有趣的过程50次
每个符文都做四个
希望这是最后一次碰它
一旦我们把所有的符文放在神秘祭坛上
我们把它们注魔成泰拉凝聚板
又一次
要求我们在上面放四件东西
希望它们不会在不知道要等多久的合成中消失
为了规避风险
我们改用魔力池作为缓冲
用一些火花来让随机的灯亮起来
这样可以牺牲帧率减小卡顿
于是我们得到了一些泰拉钢
我们堆了很多东西来获得可观速度
我们用泰拉钢做的一个精灵传送门
这个传送门能输入垃圾，并输出垃圾
有了那些新垃圾
召唤盖亚所需的盖亚水晶便可以制造了
与mod的其余部分不同
这个Boss外观平平无奇
出于某种原因，它免疫投掷物
打败它之后
我们得到了一些盖亚之魂作为回报
用来制作第一个盖亚魂锭
并召唤上个boss的兄弟
现在只需要刷一些boss
直到凑够所有致密盖亚板
一旦我们制造了新机器
我们快速制作一个龙蛋
这样
我们就可以用普通材料制作龙血
但是一旦我们尝试这样做
却遇到了一个问题
我们得把这机器升级到三级
这需要双足飞龙聚合机械方块
我们勉强能做
主要问题是
我们需要太空采矿模块MK3
虽然制作它不难
使用它
我们还需要MK3太空电梯加速轨道
这些需要一些奇怪的材料
我们将在高科技风的下一集完成
那么教训呢？
是啊，毕竟
奴役蜜蜂或许并非坏事
它们也在进化
能够制造电子产品
所以下季来点电动马达蜜蜂
拜拜
（funny：有趣，奇怪；跟原作者聊完，他也想表达反讽的“幽默”的意思）
（*Garbage in, garbage out 是AI领域的重要定律）